Nothing.
Both pockets are empty.
Other than this piece of paper.
The scent's out of the pocket now.
Could it be...
Huh?
This is just a blank sheet of paper.
What?!
Oh, Shosuke!
Talk about falling for the obvious.
You know, you should
really be more careful.
I warned you about the fire damage.
Maybe try listening next time.
I don't understand why you
are getting so worked up.
It's a normal back.
It's over for me.
This is the end.
I'm finished.
I can't explain it,
but I have this horrible feeling that
I'll die if someone sees my back!
What?
It's too late now!
I was gonna die! I'm sorry.
Just calm down.
It's my fault.
My curiosity got the best of me.
What?
He was attacked by a stand!
Damn thing must have been
attached to his back!
Which explains why Heaven's Door couldn't
reveal it when he arrived at the house.
It was already too late by that point.
That stand attached itself
to him before he got here.
The architect isn't a user, he's a victim.
He was used like a meat
puppet to get to me!
Piggyback, please.
It's here.
It's the enemy's stand.
Let's play piggyback, okay?
Piggyback, please?
How about it?
Can we play piggyback, please?
Breakdown, breakdown!
Listen, breakdown, breakdown!
Let's go!
heart of the heart The light
of the heart The light of
the heart The spirit of the
heart The light of the heart
Let the voice of love Take
you higher The power of the
power The power of the heart
Kira's Disappearance?
Here's a list of missing persons
cases in Morioh, including runaways.
The data's from the period
after Kira's disappearance?
Hence the small number.
You're of the mind that
some of those people
could be Kira's victims
makes a lot of sense!
It's a possibility, but we can't
know that for sure at this point.
We have to follow his
every conceivable move.
It doesn't matter how
insignificant the activity seems
any action he takes can
have far-reaching effects.
They always do
Piggyback, please.
Heaven's door, attack!
Hey, piggyback, please. What the?
I don't believe it.
The damn thing has
attached itself to my back.
Is this because of the architect?
Because I looked at his back? Blast it!
Ignite the pictures.
Please ignite the
pictures you've collected?
Ignite the what?
You heard what I said?
Now get rid of those pesky pictures!
What do you mean?
The pictures I took Could one of
them lead us to Yoshikage Kira?
That's it, isn't it?
You're attempting a cover-up Just
set all the pictures on fire Please,
you'll do it, won't you?
Please?
Shut up, you leech!
Heaven's door!
I've got it!
How about I read your powers
that inscribe my mandate?
What the hell?
Shit!
I am known as Cheap Trap,
and I was given life when my
Sazokinoto was impaled by the arrow.
But since he croaked,
my user is Rorankishibe!
I've relocated to you!
You're my user now whether
you want to be or not!
Get it now?
When you attack me with a stand, all
you're doing is hurting yourself.
Scary, right?
I am a stand with a will of my own.
Sure, Masazo Kinoto birthed me,
but he didn't have the wherewithal
to control me as a stand user.
I filled his mind with lots
of horrifying whispers,
and the terror of his bony back being
seen consumed him at the very end,
wouldn't you say?
You understand? Yes?
Tell me you do!
You get it, yes?
I whisper fear into the ears of my host.
Now that you know my
power, burn those pictures!
Dirty leech, get off me!
Damn you bastard!
I swear I'll get you off my back!
If that's what you want, all
you have to do is show me off!
Just show someone your back!
Yes, I'll leave you and
attach to another soul.
It just takes a flash.
Afternoon, Rohan-sensei.
I'm an avid reader of your work, though
you might want to try some nudes.
Nude women, that is.
Catch you later.
Let's burn those photos, yes.
Shiosuke!
He...
he caught the bullet.
Damn, you asshole!
Shining diamond, eh?
Well, I guess the rumors were true.
You can indeed handle a bullet at
point-blank range without an issue.
This is freaky, isn't it?
Now chomp down on that lip, Josuke.
He's almost there. Bite it!
Show me that bite.
Show me your mark of fear!
That sheet of paper must be a stand!
It has to be, since it's as pathetic
as that geezer in the photo!
Still won't bite, eh?
Seems he's trying to cover
up his fear with anger.
If that's the case, I suppose
it's time for the big reveal.
You cocky bastard!
You're dead!
Something about this doesn't feel right.
He's been hiding this whole time.
Why would he choose to show himself now?
This is all a trap.
He made himself appear
so you'd attack him.
This guy's dangerous!
Get the hell out of there, Josuke!
You know you were right a moment ago
when you said I had a pathetic stand.
But it's not all bad, I guess.
Its ability allows me to
transform almost anything into
a piece of paper to be filed
discreetly and conveniently.
And this slip of paper contains
Koichi Hirose. Bastard!
So you've had Koichi this entire time!
I'm picking up Koichi's scent again.
He wasn't holding on to
one of his belongings!
He had Koichi!
Rest assured, he's alive.
I'm the user of a pathetic
third-rate stand ride.
It doesn't have the
power or ability to kill.
However, if someone were to tear it into
little pieces, that's a different story.
I'm gonna let you off easy.
Bring Koichi back now, and I'll
only beat you down to a bloody pulp.
Go ahead and take him.
I'd like to see you try.
Koichi!
As you said earlier,
my stand isn't the most powerful and
it doesn't have the ability to kill.
But if it were to be ripped to shreds...
I wouldn't go after that
paper if I were you.
It has to be a trap!
Shosuke, ignore it!
Ah, at long last!
You bit it!
Mysterioso was waiting for this moment!
Josuke Higashikata, the moment you
bit your lip, you sealed your fate.
You devious dickhead!
You just revealed your mark of fear.
You can attempt to resist all you like.
You are now powerless before Mysterioso.
Sorry, Josuke, but I'm glad
we made that agreement.
If I had tried to help, he
would have gotten me first.
I am the one with the
scent discerning abilities.
Now that you've fallen prey to its power,
do you understand why Mysterioso's
the most unstoppable force ever seen?
What?
How the hell did you get out?
His stand is repairing the metal pole,
and he's using the energy to escape.
The piece of paper you're holding.
If I looked inside, I'm
guessing I wouldn't find Koichi.
I knew from the start that was just a dirty
decoy with Koichi Hirose written on it.
The only reason you had the
confidence to reveal your true self
to me was because you still had
the real Koichi held hostage.
Keeping him alive is the only way
for you to maintain your leverage.
I knew that piece of paper was
just a trap to lure me into danger.
Looks like I was right.
But even so, I still had no other choice
but to go after that stupid scrap of paper.
Despite it being a trap,
there was still a chance you'd thrown
the real Koichi toward that car.
And when it comes to my friends,
I don't care if it's a 1 % chance!
Losing them is a risk that
I'm just not willing to take.
Mysterioso can have the win for now.
It sucks, but there's not much more
Shining Diamond can do at this point.
That said,
let me give you a piece of advice before
I become one of your paper prisoners.
Rip me to oblivion the
moment I finish folding.
Cause if I'm able to make it
out of this bullshit trap alive,
I'll freaking kill you!
That's a pretty loud bark you had there.
It's too bad you didn't
have the bite to match.
Yuya Fungami, allow me to commend you.
Not assisting Josuke was a very wise move.
I could have easily disposed
of you had you tried.
Your mark of fear is a stroke of the chin.
In fact, you're doing it right now.
But the old man in the photo
never ordered me to kill you,
so I suppose your death has been
postponed for the time being.
Smart move, my friend.
Want to hear something interesting?
This paper it's tough but
anyone can release its contents.
By unfolding it straightforward?
Yes but for someone consumed with fear
it's surprisingly It's becoming difficult.
Mariah Grand Hotel, please.
Excellent!
Keicho Hirose and Josuke
Higashikata have been disposed of!
Rohan Kishibe should be enjoying
the same fate about now!
Which one?
Which one exposes Yoshikage Kira?
Which picture is that
old man so worried about?
Just burn them all, okay?
No use.
There just aren't enough clues
for me to figure this out.
Well then, let's burn them, yes?
Shut your mouth, you pest! Damn it.
I have to let them know.
Someone needs to know what's going on!
Uh, that was Mariah Grand Hotel, right?
Yes, that is correct.
Are you spending the night?
Not sure, though I do have a
lot of work to take care of.
A lot of work, indeed.
No, I cannot allow you
to reach that hotel.
Dammit, Josuke, you're
such a pompous asshole.
Seeing you get captured makes
me think about my darling girls.
I can't believe I'm saying this!
but if any one of my loving,
supportive vixens was ever turned
into a piece of paper, I'd...
I don't even want to think about it,
but if they were nabbed by this creep...
I'd do the same thing to get them back!
If I let you or Kira get away,
I'd never be able to look at
myself in the mirror again!
I order you to release Koichi!
I rescind my earlier statement.
This is a most unwise decision.
Listen, I'm not sure you really
want to take me on, coward.
Doing so would instantly make
you an enemy of Kira's father.
But so be it!
63, 64, and 65.
It's not a tank, but Highway
Kick is a relentless hunter.
If you think you're
getting away, you're wrong!
And stopped.
But why?
We're not at the hotel yet.
And it doesn't look like
anybody's in the taxi.
Huh. Strange.
I'm still picking up
his scent from the car.
But how?
Where the hell is he?
Where could he have run off to?
Ugh, the scent of this paper.
There's no question.
This paper smells like Koichi and Josuke.
Wait, Highway Kick, don't
open the door just yet.
The bastard thinks I'm an idiot.
This is clearly another trap.
So he's attempting to lure me in, huh?
Fine, I accept your challenge.
Did you hear me?
I said I'd fight!
He wants me to be afraid, that's obvious.
But the question is, how's he gonna do it?
I've gotta find out.
What the?
What's this piece of
paper stuck in the door?
He's underestimating me again.
But based on this scent, I'm
sure the paper is a trap.
And I figured out what kind it is, too.
I'm opening the door, Highway Kick.
This guy can turn fire into paper, too?
I've seen through your little trick.
Josuke, Koichi, I'm gonna
get you out of there!
But unless my nose is lying to me,
there's something else lurking
in there besides those two.
Wait, I'm gonna have to go
about this very carefully.
How strange.
It's like that other
smell is moving around.
It's faint, but I think
it's coming from...
What?
Crap!
Highway Kick!
What the heck is this stuff?
Wait, I think it's some kind of chemical.
Shit!
One thing after another.
Wait a sec. What's this?
Now I'm getting a nose full of iron.
Okay, just calm down.
Remember, he wants me to be scared.
If I allow him to freak
me out, he wins. Iron.
What is it? A machine?
Screw this shit!
I just have to open the damn paper!
Shosuke! Koichi!
This doesn't make any sense!
How the hell can it stand
hide electricity and paper?
And if this predicament wasn't bad enough,
I'm smelling that horrible
mechanical stench again, but why?
It's the Shredder!
It won't turn off!
It's bullying in Josuke and Koichi! Damn!
Highway Kick!
It's no use!
Highway Go-Go's too weak!
It's not capable of stopping this thing!
No!
Josuke Koichi!
So you finally gave in, Yuya Fungami.
The onset of fear, followed
by a touch to the chin.
Though fear just isn't your look.
Scaring the ever-loving shit out
of you was surprisingly simple.
Yuya Fungami.
Mysterioso can turn absolutely
anyone into a piece of paper.
Anyone, anytime!
Really?
That's what makes your stance so amazing?
It instantly transforms
its target into paper!
Isn't that great?
I admit it, you win.
You really got me there.
Although, I couldn't be happier to lose.
After all, if I wasn't
a flimsy piece of paper,
I wouldn't be able to
reach inside this shredder!
Wait!
What did you just pull out of there?
You better not unfold that sheet of paper!
Totally worth it.
I'd turn into paper any day
to see that look on your face.
Yuya Fungami. Well, damn.
After that, I gotta say, you're a
cooler dude than I took you for.
You stay the hell away
from me or else I'll
take this paper and I'll rip it to pieces.
Would you really sacrifice
Yu-Yafu-Gami like that?
Act three! Three! Freeze!
This pressure!
I'm trying to remember
what I said earlier.
I know I'm forgetting something,
but I don't know what it is.
Oh yeah, it's coming back.
I think I said I'd kill you
when I got out of there.
Yep, that is definitely what I said.
Oh, yeah.
I think I also said something about
never forgiving someone as vile as you.
Someone who takes hostages.
Someone who uses psychological
blackmail to screw with someone.
Let's just take a beat.
All I wanted to do was observe people's
reaction to fear stimuli, I swear.
I just acquired my stand a bit
ago, so I guess I got carried away.
I'm so sorry for my actions.
I feel like an absolute heal.
You know what?
I've actually noticed something about you.
Huh?
When you get scared, I'm pretty sure
one of your eyes squints involuntarily.
I guess you could say it's a habit.
But, when you're really losing your
shit, you close both your eyes.
so you like observing people huh
then please knock yourself out but
you're gonna keep your mouth shut
and behave yourself understand the
young mysterioso Terunosuke miyamoto
human book and out of commission
josuke never bothered reading it
but instead donated it to the Mariah
Library.
Mention Mysterioso to any librarian and
they'll let you read it, but borrowing it is
forbidden.
Don't be surprised if you hear a
faint voice while perusing its pages.
Well, that's taken
care of.
So why do I feel like
I've spoken too soon?
At the very least, this means we've gotten
one step closer to
capturing Yoshikage Kira.
Maybe, but we still
don't have a single clue.
Damn it all!
They're resilient little crotch crawlers!
Calling your friends for
help isn't going to work.
You have some photos to burn now. Yes?
Huh?
Alright, I'm heading out for a bit.
Hmm?
Where are you running off to?
To go and find our leads
as soon as possible,
I'll investigate where each
missing person was last seen.
No one can escape from their
innate personality for very long.
He'll make his move soon.
I'll catch him.
I'll find proof that he's not my real dad.
I will!
Anytime I need to see a
face, it has closed my eyes.
And I am taken to a place
with a crystal mine.
I'm a gentle feeling.
Take a shelter in the face of my spine.
Straight like a Chaka cherry cola.
I don't need to try to
explain how to hold on tight.
And if it happens again,
I'ma move so slightly to the
arms and the lips and the face.
So the human kind of all
that I need to, I want to.
Come and stand a little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what
hit you when I get to you.
Oh, I want you.
I don't know if I need you.
But oh, I gotta find you.
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you, but ooh,
I've got to find you.